Inside Albany Records
Inside Albany Records
- Videorecordings
  - Videorecordings, 1978
    - No. 445, 1978-05-03; 3/4 inch videotape: U-matic; master; 00:30:00; inside_albany_0155 (Box 18)
    - No. 446, 1978-05-12; 3/4 inch videotape: U-matic; master; 00:30:00; inside_albany_0152; tape labeled as no. 442 but slate reads no. 446 (this is episode no. 446) (Box 17)
    - No. 446, 1978-05-12; 3/4 inch videotape: U-matic; dub; 00:30:00; inside_albany_0156; duplicate (Box 18)
    - No. 447, 1978-05-18; 3/4 inch videotape: U-matic; master; 00:30:00; inside_albany_0157 (Box 18)
    - No. 448, 1978-05-26; 3/4 inch videotape: U-matic; master; 00:30:00; inside_albany_0158 (Box 18)
    - No. 449, 1978-06-02; 3/4 inch videotape: U-matic; master; 00:30:00; inside_albany_0159 (Box 18)
    - No. 450, 1978-06-09; 3/4 inch videotape: U-matic; master; 00:30:00; inside_albany_0160 (Box 18)
    - No. 452, 1978-06-23; 3/4 inch videotape: U-matic; master; 00:30:00; inside_albany_0161 (Box 18)
    - No. 501, 1978-06-30; 3/4 inch videotape: U-matic; master; 00:30:00; inside_albany_0162 (Box 18)
    - No. 502, 1978-07-07; 3/4 inch videotape: U-matic; master; 00:30:00; inside_albany_0163 (Box 18)
    - No. 503, 1978-07-14; 3/4 inch videotape: U-matic; master; 00:30:00; inside_albany_0164 (Box 19)
    - No. 504, 1978-07-21; 3/4 inch videotape: U-matic; master; 00:30:00; inside_albany_0165 (Box 19)
    - No. 504, 1978-07-21; 3/4 inch videotape: U-matic; dub; 00:30:00; inside_albany_0166; duplicate (Box 19)
    - No. 505, 1978-07-28; 3/4 inch videotape: U-matic; master; 00:30:00; inside_albany_0167 (Box 19)
    - No. 506, 1978-08-04; 3/4 inch videotape: U-matic; master; 00:30:00; inside_albany_0169 (Box 19)
    - No. 507, 1978-08-10; 3/4 inch videotape: U-matic; master; 00:30:00; inside_albany_0170 (Box 19)
    - No. 508, 1978-08-18; 3/4 inch videotape: U-matic; master; 00:30:00; inside_albany_0171 (Box 19)
    - No. 508, 1978-08-18; 3/4 inch videotape: U-matic; dub; 00:30:00; inside_albany_0168; duplicate (Box 19)
    - No. 509, 1978-08-25; 3/4 inch videotape: U-matic; master; 00:30:00; inside_albany_0172 (Box 19)
    - No. 510, 1978-09-01; 3/4 inch videotape: U-matic; master; 00:30:00; inside_albany_0173 (Box 19)
    - No. 511, 1978-09-08; 3/4 inch videotape: U-matic; master; 00:30:00; inside_albany_0174 (Box 20)
    - No. 512, 1978-09-13; 3/4 inch videotape: U-matic; master; 00:30:00; inside_albany_0175 (Box 20)
    - No. 513, 1978-09-20; 3/4 inch videotape: U-matic; master; 00:30:00; inside_albany_0176 (Box 20)
    - No. 514, 1978-09-29; 3/4 inch videotape: U-matic; master; 00:30:00; inside_albany_0177 (Box 20)
    - No. 515, 1978-10-06; 3/4 inch videotape: U-matic; master; 00:30:00; inside_albany_0178 (Box 20)
    - No. 516, 1978-10-14; 3/4 inch videotape: U-matic; master; 00:30:00; inside_albany_0179 (Box 20)
    - No. 517, 1978-10-20; 3/4 inch videotape: U-matic; master; 00:30:00; inside_albany_0180 (Box 20)
    - No. 518, 1978-10-27; 3/4 inch videotape: U-matic; master; 00:30:00; inside_albany_0181 (Box 20)
    - No. 519, 1978-11-03; 3/4 inch videotape: U-matic; master; 00:30:00; inside_albany_0182 (Box 20)
    - No. 520, 1978-11-10; 3/4 inch videotape: U-matic; master; 00:30:00; inside_albany_0183 (Box 20)
    - No. 521, 1978-11-17; 3/4 inch videotape: U-matic; master; 00:30:00; inside_albany_0184 (Box 21)
    - No. 522, 1978-11-22; 3/4 inch videotape: U-matic; master; 00:30:00; inside_albany_0185 (Box 21)
    - No. 523, 1978-12-01; 3/4 inch videotape: U-matic; master; 00:30:00; inside_albany_0186 (Box 21)
    - No. 524, 1978-12-08; 3/4 inch videotape: U-matic; master; 00:30:00; inside_albany_0187 (Box 21)
    - No. 525, 1978-12-15; 3/4 inch videotape: U-matic; master; 00:30:00; inside_albany_0188 (Box 21)
    - No. 526, 1978-12-21; 3/4 inch videotape: U-matic; master; 00:30:00; inside_albany_0189 (Box 21)
    - No. 527, 1978-12-29; 3/4 inch videotape: U-matic; master; 00:30:00; inside_albany_0190 (Box 21)
  - Videorecordings, 1979
    - No. 528, 1979-01-05; 3/4 inch videotape: U-matic; master; 00:30:00; inside_albany_0191 (Box 21)
    - No. 529, 1979-01-12; 3/4 inch videotape: U-matic; master; 00:30:00; inside_albany_0192 (Box 21)
    - No. 530, 1979-01-18; 3/4 inch videotape: U-matic; master; 00:30:00; inside_albany_0193 (Box 21)
    - No. 531, 1979-01-26; 3/4 inch videotape: U-matic; master; 00:30:00; inside_albany_0194 (Box 22)
    - No. 532, 1979-02-02; 3/4 inch videotape: U-matic; master; 00:30:00; inside_albany_0195 (Box 22)
    - No. 533, 1979-02-09; 3/4 inch videotape: U-matic; master; 00:30:00; inside_albany_0196 (Box 22)
    - No. 534, 1979-02-14; 3/4 inch videotape: U-matic; master; 00:30:00; inside_albany_0197 (Box 22)
    - No. 535, 1979-02-23; 3/4 inch videotape: U-matic; master; 00:30:00; inside_albany_0198 (Box 22)
    - No. 536, 1979-03-02; 3/4 inch videotape: U-matic; master; 00:30:00; inside_albany_0199 (Box 22)
    - No. 537, 1979-03-09; 3/4 inch videotape: U-matic; master; 00:30:00; inside_albany_0200 (Box 22)
    - No. 538, 1979-03-16; 3/4 inch videotape: U-matic; master; 00:30:00; inside_albany_0201 (Box 22)
    - No. 539, 1979-03-23; 3/4 inch videotape: U-matic; master; 00:30:00; inside_albany_0202 (Box 22)
    - No. 540, 1979-03-30; 3/4 inch videotape: U-matic; master; 00:30:00; inside_albany_0203 (Box 22)
    - No. 541, 1979-04-06; 3/4 inch videotape: U-matic; master; 00:30:00; inside_albany_0204 (Box 23)
    - No. 542, 1979-04-13; 3/4 inch videotape: U-matic; master; 00:30:00; inside_albany_0205 (Box 23)
    - No. 543, 1979-04-20; 3/4 inch videotape: U-matic; master; 00:30:00; inside_albany_0206 (Box 23)
    - No. 544, 1979-04-28; 3/4 inch videotape: U-matic; master; 00:30:00; inside_albany_0207 (Box 23)
    - No. 545, 1979-05-04; 3/4 inch videotape: U-matic; master; 00:30:00; inside_albany_0208 (Box 23)
    - No. 546, 1979-05-11; 3/4 inch videotape: U-matic; master; 00:30:00; inside_albany_0209 (Box 23)
    - No. 547, 1979-05-18; 3/4 inch videotape: U-matic; master; 00:30:00; inside_albany_0210 (Box 23)
    - No. 548, 1979-05-25; 3/4 inch videotape: U-matic; master; 00:30:00; inside_albany_0211 (Box 23)
    - No. 549, 1979-06-01; 3/4 inch videotape: U-matic; master; 00:30:00; inside_albany_0212 (Box 23)
    - No. 550, 1979-06-08; 3/4 inch videotape: U-matic; master; 00:30:00; inside_albany_0213 (Box 23)
    - No. 551, 1979-06-15; 3/4 inch videotape: U-matic; master; 00:30:00; inside_albany_0214 (Box 24)
    - No. 552, 1979-06-22; 3/4 inch videotape: U-matic; master; 00:30:00; inside_albany_0215 (Box 24)
    - No. 601, 1979-06-29; 3/4 inch videotape: U-matic; master; 00:30:00; inside_albany_0216 (Box 24)
    - No. 602, 1979-07-02; 3/4 inch videotape: U-matic; master; 00:30:00; inside_albany_0217 (Box 24)
    - No. 603, 1979-07-13; 3/4 inch videotape: U-matic; master; 00:30:00; inside_albany_0218; tape labeled as no. 602 but slate reads no. 603 (this is episode no. 603) (Box 24)
    - No. 604, 1979-07-20; 3/4 inch videotape: U-matic; master; 00:30:00; inside_albany_0219 (Box 24)
    - No. 605, 1979-07-27; 3/4 inch videotape: U-matic; master; 00:30:00; inside_albany_0220 (Box 24)
    - No. 606, 1979-08-03; 3/4 inch videotape: U-matic; master; 00:30:00; inside_albany_0221 (Box 24)
    - No. 607, 1979-08-10; 3/4 inch videotape: U-matic; master; 00:30:00; inside_albany_0222 (Box 24)
    - No. 608, 1979-08-17; 3/4 inch videotape: U-matic; master; 00:30:00; inside_albany_0223 (Box 24)
    - No. 609, 1979-08-24; 3/4 inch videotape: U-matic; master; 00:30:00; inside_albany_0224 (Box 24)
    - No. 610, 1979-08-31; 3/4 inch videotape: U-matic; master; 00:30:00; inside_albany_0225 (Box 25)
    - No. 611, 1979-09-07; 3/4 inch videotape: U-matic; master; 00:30:00; inside_albany_0226 (Box 25)
    - No. 612, 1979-09-14; 3/4 inch videotape: U-matic; master; 00:30:00; inside_albany_0227 (Box 25)
    - No. 613, 1979-09-21; 2 inch videotape: Quad; master; 00:30:00; inside_albany_0228 (Box 47)
    - No. 613, 1979-09-21; 3/4 inch videotape: U-matic; dub; 00:30:00; inside_albany_0229; duplicate (Box 25)
    - No. 614, 1979-09-28; 3/4 inch videotape: U-matic; master; 00:30:00; inside_albany_0230 (Box 25)
    - No. 615, 1979-10-05; 3/4 inch videotape: U-matic; master; 00:30:00; inside_albany_0231 (Box 25)
    - No. 616, 1979-10-12; 3/4 inch videotape: U-matic; master; 00:30:00; inside_albany_0232 (Box 25)
    - No. 617, 1979-10-19; 3/4 inch videotape: U-matic; master; 00:30:00; inside_albany_0233 (Box 25)
    - No. 618, 1979-10-26; 3/4 inch videotape: U-matic; master; 00:30:00; inside_albany_0234 (Box 25)
    - No. 619, 1979-11-02; 3/4 inch videotape: U-matic; master; 00:30:00; inside_albany_0235 (Box 25)
    - No. 620, 1979-11-09; 3/4 inch videotape: U-matic; master; 00:30:00; inside_albany_0236 (Box 26)
    - No. 621, 1979-11-16; 3/4 inch videotape: U-matic; master; 00:30:00; inside_albany_0237 (Box 26)
    - No. 622, 1979-11-20; 3/4 inch videotape: U-matic; master; 00:30:00; inside_albany_0238 (Box 26)
    - No. 623, 1979-11-30; 3/4 inch videotape: U-matic; master; 00:30:00; inside_albany_0239 (Box 26)
    - No. 624, 1979-12-07; 3/4 inch videotape: U-matic; master; 00:30:00; inside_albany_0240 (Box 26)
    - No. 625, 1979-12-14; 3/4 inch videotape: U-matic; master; 00:30:00; inside_albany_0241 (Box 26)
    - No. 626, 1979-12-21; 3/4 inch videotape: U-matic; master; 00:30:00; inside_albany_0242 (Box 26)
    - No. 627, 1979-12-28; 3/4 inch videotape: U-matic; master; 00:30:00; inside_albany_0243 (Box 26)
  - Videorecordings, 1980
    - No. 628, 1980-01-04; 3/4 inch videotape: U-matic; master; 00:30:00; inside_albany_0244 (Box 26)
    - No. 629, 1980-01-11; 3/4 inch videotape: U-matic; master; 00:30:00; inside_albany_0245 (Box 26)
    - No. 630, 1980-01-18; 3/4 inch videotape: U-matic; master; 00:30:00; inside_albany_0246 (Box 27)
    - No. 631, 1980-01-25; 3/4 inch videotape: U-matic; master; 00:30:00; inside_albany_0247 (Box 27)
    - No. 632, 1980-02-01; 3/4 inch videotape: U-matic; master; 00:30:00; inside_albany_0248 (Box 27)
    - No. 633, 1980-02-08; 3/4 inch videotape: U-matic; master; 00:30:00; inside_albany_0249 (Box 27)
    - No. 634, 1980-02-15; 3/4 inch videotape: U-matic; master; 00:30:00; inside_albany_0250 (Box 27)
    - No. 635, 1980-02-22; 3/4 inch videotape: U-matic; master; 00:30:00; inside_albany_0251 (Box 27)
    - No. 636, 1980-02-29; 3/4 inch videotape: U-matic; master; 00:30:00; inside_albany_0252 (Box 27)
    - No. 637, 1980-03-07; 3/4 inch videotape: U-matic; master; 00:30:00; inside_albany_0253 (Box 27)
    - No. 638, 1980-03-14; 3/4 inch videotape: U-matic; master; 00:30:00; inside_albany_0254 (Box 27)
    - No. 639, 1980-03-21; 3/4 inch videotape: U-matic; master; 00:30:00; inside_albany_0255 (Box 27)
    - No. 640, 1980-03-28; 3/4 inch videotape: U-matic; master; 00:30:00; inside_albany_0256 (Box 28)
    - No. 641, 1980-04-04; 3/4 inch videotape: U-matic; master; 00:30:00; inside_albany_0257 (Box 28)
    - No. 642, 1980-04-11; 3/4 inch videotape: U-matic; master; 00:30:00; inside_albany_0258 (Box 28)
    - No. 643, 1980-04-18; 3/4 inch videotape: U-matic; master; 00:30:00; inside_albany_0259 (Box 28)
    - No. 644, 1980-04-25; 3/4 inch videotape: U-matic; master; 00:30:00; inside_albany_0260 (Box 28)
    - No. 645, 1980-05-02; 3/4 inch videotape: U-matic; master; 00:30:00; inside_albany_0261 (Box 28)
    - No. 646, 1980-05-09; 3/4 inch videotape: U-matic; master; 00:30:00; inside_albany_0262 (Box 28)
    - No. 647, 1980-05-16; 3/4 inch videotape: U-matic; master; 00:30:00; inside_albany_0263 (Box 28)
    - No. 648, 1980-05-23; 3/4 inch videotape: U-matic; master; 00:30:00; inside_albany_0264 (Box 28)
    - No. 649, 1980-05-30; 3/4 inch videotape: U-matic; master; 00:30:00; inside_albany_0265 (Box 28)
    - No. 650, 1980-06-06; 3/4 inch videotape: U-matic; master; 00:30:00; inside_albany_0266 (Box 29)
    - No. 651, 1980-06-14; 3/4 inch videotape: U-matic; master; 00:30:00; inside_albany_0267 (Box 29)
    - No. 652, 1980-06-20; 2 inch videotape: Quad; master; 00:30:00; inside_albany_0268 (Box 47)
    - No. 652, 1980-06-20; 3/4 inch videotape: U-matic; dub; 00:30:00; inside_albany_0269; duplicate (Box 29)
    - No. 701, 1980-06-27; 3/4 inch videotape: U-matic; master; 00:30:00; inside_albany_0270 (Box 29)
    - No. 702, 1980-07-03; 3/4 inch videotape: U-matic; master; 00:30:00; inside_albany_0271 (Box 29)
    - No. 703, 1980-07-11; 3/4 inch videotape: U-matic; master; 00:30:00; inside_albany_0272 (Box 29)
    - No. 704, 1980-07-18; 3/4 inch videotape: U-matic; master; 00:30:00; inside_albany_0273 (Box 29)
    - No. 705, 1980-07-25; 2 inch videotape: Quad; master; 00:30:00; inside_albany_0274 (Box 47)
    - No. 705, 1980-07-25; 3/4 inch videotape: U-matic; dub; 00:30:00; inside_albany_0275; duplicate (Box 29)
    - No. 706, 1980-08-01; 3/4 inch videotape: U-matic; master; 00:30:00; inside_albany_0276 (Box 29)
    - No. 707, 1980-08-08; 3/4 inch videotape: U-matic; master; 00:30:00; inside_albany_0277 (Box 29)
    - No. 708, 1980-08-15; 3/4 inch videotape: U-matic; master; 00:30:00; inside_albany_0278 (Box 30)
    - No. 709, 1980-08-22; 3/4 inch videotape: U-matic; master; 00:30:00; inside_albany_0279 (Box 30)
    - No. 710, 1980-08-29; 3/4 inch videotape: U-matic; master; 00:30:00; inside_albany_0280 (Box 30)
    - No. 711, 1980-09-05; 3/4 inch videotape: U-matic; master; 00:30:00; inside_albany_0281 (Box 30)
    - No. 712, 1980-09-12; 3/4 inch videotape: U-matic; master; 00:30:00; inside_albany_0282 (Box 30)
    - No. 713, 1980-09-19; 3/4 inch videotape: U-matic; master; 00:30:00; inside_albany_0283 (Box 30)
    - No. 714, 1980-09-27; 3/4 inch videotape: U-matic; master; 00:30:00; inside_albany_0284 (Box 30)
    - No. 715, 1980-10-03; 3/4 inch videotape: U-matic; master; 00:30:00; inside_albany_0285 (Box 30)
    - No. 716, 1980-10-10; 3/4 inch videotape: U-matic; master; 00:30:00; inside_albany_0286 (Box 30)
    - No. 717, 1980-10-17; 3/4 inch videotape: U-matic; master; 00:30:00; inside_albany_0287 (Box 30)
    - No. 718, 1980-10-24; 3/4 inch videotape: U-matic; master; 00:30:00; inside_albany_0288 (Box 31)
    - No. 719, 1980-11-01; 3/4 inch videotape: U-matic; master; 00:30:00; inside_albany_0289 (Box 31)
    - No. 720, 1980-11-07; 3/4 inch videotape: U-matic; master; 00:30:00; inside_albany_0290 (Box 31)
    - No. 721, 1980-11-14; 3/4 inch videotape: U-matic; master; 00:30:00; inside_albany_0291 (Box 31)
    - No. 722, 1980-11-21; 3/4 inch videotape: U-matic; master; 00:30:00; inside_albany_0292 (Box 31)
    - No. 723, 1980-11-26; 3/4 inch videotape: U-matic; master; 00:30:00; inside_albany_0293 (Box 31)
    - No. 724, 1980-12-05; 3/4 inch videotape: U-matic; master; 00:30:00; inside_albany_0294 (Box 31)
    - No. 725, 1980-12-12; 3/4 inch videotape: U-matic; master; 00:30:00; inside_albany_0295 (Box 31)
    - No. 726, 1980-12-19; 3/4 inch videotape: U-matic; master; 00:30:00; inside_albany_0296 (Box 31)
    - No. 727, 1980-12-24; 3/4 inch videotape: U-matic; master; 00:30:00; inside_albany_0297 (Box 31)
  - Videorecordings, 1981
    - No. 728, 1981-01-03; 3/4 inch videotape: U-matic; master; 00:30:00; inside_albany_0298 (Box 32)
    - No. 729, 1981-01-10; 3/4 inch videotape: U-matic; master; 00:30:00; inside_albany_0299 (Box 32)
    - No. 730, 1981-01-16; 3/4 inch videotape: U-matic; master; 00:30:00; inside_albany_0300 (Box 32)
    - No. 731, 1981-01-23; 3/4 inch videotape: U-matic; master; 00:30:00; inside_albany_0301 (Box 32)
    - No. 732, 1981-01-30; 3/4 inch videotape: U-matic; master; 00:30:00; inside_albany_0302 (Box 32)
    - No. 733, 1981-02-06; 3/4 inch videotape: U-matic; master; 00:30:00; inside_albany_0303 (Box 32)
    - No. 734, 1981-02-13; 3/4 inch videotape: U-matic; master; 00:30:00; inside_albany_0304 (Box 32)
    - No. 735, 1981-02-20; 3/4 inch videotape: U-matic; master; 00:30:00; inside_albany_0305 (Box 32)
    - No. 736, 1981-02-27; 3/4 inch videotape: U-matic; master; 00:30:00; inside_albany_0306 (Box 32)
    - No. 737, 1981-03-06; 3/4 inch videotape: U-matic; master; 00:30:00; inside_albany_0307 (Box 32)
    - No. 738, 1981-03-13; 3/4 inch videotape: U-matic; master; 00:30:00; inside_albany_0308 (Box 33)
    - No. 739, 1981-03-20; 3/4 inch videotape: U-matic; master; 00:30:00; inside_albany_0309 (Box 33)
    - No. 740, 1981-03-27; 3/4 inch videotape: U-matic; master; 00:30:00; inside_albany_0310 (Box 33)
    - No. 741, 1981-04-03; 3/4 inch videotape: U-matic; master; 00:30:00; inside_albany_0311 (Box 33)
    - No. 742, 1981-04-10; 3/4 inch videotape: U-matic; master; 00:30:00; inside_albany_0312 (Box 33)
    - No. 743, 1981-04-17; 3/4 inch videotape: U-matic; master; 00:30:00; inside_albany_0313 (Box 33)
    - No. 744, 1981-04-24; 3/4 inch videotape: U-matic; master; 00:30:00; inside_albany_0314 (Box 33)
    - No. 745, 1981-05-01; 3/4 inch videotape: U-matic; master; 00:30:00; inside_albany_0315 (Box 33)
    - No. 746, 1981-05-08; 3/4 inch videotape: U-matic; master; 00:30:00; inside_albany_0316 (Box 33)
    - No. 747, 1981-05-15; 3/4 inch videotape: U-matic; master; 00:30:00; inside_albany_0317 (Box 33)
    - No. 748, 1981-05-22; 3/4 inch videotape: U-matic; master; 00:30:00; inside_albany_0318 (Box 34)
    - No. 749, 1981-05-29; 3/4 inch videotape: U-matic; master; 00:30:00; inside_albany_0319 (Box 34)
    - No. 750, 1981-06-05; 3/4 inch videotape: U-matic; master; 00:30:00; inside_albany_0320 (Box 34)
    - No. 751, 1981-06-13; 3/4 inch videotape: U-matic; master; 00:30:00; inside_albany_0321 (Box 34)
    - No. 752, 1981-06-20; 3/4 inch videotape: U-matic; master; 00:30:00; inside_albany_0322 (Box 34)
    - No. 752, 1981-06-20; VHS; dub; 00:30:00; inside_albany_0750; duplicate (Box 46)
    - No. 801, 1981-06-26; 3/4 inch videotape: U-matic; master; 00:30:00; inside_albany_0323 (Box 34)
    - No. 802, 1981-07-04; 3/4 inch videotape: U-matic; master; 00:30:00; inside_albany_0324 (Box 34)
    - No. 803, 1981-07-10; 3/4 inch videotape: U-matic; master; 00:30:00; inside_albany_0325 (Box 34)
    - No. 804, 1981-07-17; 3/4 inch videotape: U-matic; master; 00:30:00; inside_albany_0326 (Box 34)
    - No. 805, 1981-07-25; 3/4 inch videotape: U-matic; master; 00:30:00; inside_albany_0327 (Box 34)
    - No. 806, 1981-07-31; 3/4 inch videotape: U-matic; master; 00:30:00; inside_albany_0328 (Box 35)
    - No. 807, 1981-08-08; 3/4 inch videotape: U-matic; master; 00:30:00; inside_albany_0329 (Box 35)
    - No. 808, 1981-08-14; 3/4 inch videotape: U-matic; master; 00:30:00; inside_albany_0330 (Box 35)
    - No. 809, 1981-08-21; 3/4 inch videotape: U-matic; master; 00:30:00; inside_albany_0331 (Box 35)
    - No. 810, 1981-08-28; 3/4 inch videotape: U-matic; master; 00:30:00; inside_albany_0332 (Box 35)
    - No. 811, 1981-09-04; 3/4 inch videotape: U-matic; master; 00:30:00; inside_albany_0333 (Box 35)
    - No. 812, 1981-09-11; 3/4 inch videotape: U-matic; master; 00:30:00; inside_albany_0334 (Box 35)
    - No. 813, 1981-09-18; 3/4 inch videotape: U-matic; master; 00:30:00; inside_albany_0335 (Box 35)
    - No. 814, 1981-09-25; 3/4 inch videotape: U-matic; master; 00:30:00; inside_albany_0336 (Box 35)
    - No. 815, 1981-10-02; 3/4 inch videotape: U-matic; master; 00:30:00; inside_albany_0337 (Box 35)
    - No. 816, 1981-10-10; 3/4 inch videotape: U-matic; master; 00:30:00; inside_albany_0338 (Box 36)
    - No. 817, 1981-10-17; 1 inch videotape: SMPTE Type C; master; 00:30:00; inside_albany_0503 (Box 47)
    - No. 818, 1981-10-24; 1 inch videotape: SMPTE Type C; master; 00:30:00; inside_albany_0503 (Box 47)
    - No. 819, 1981-10-31; 1 inch videotape: SMPTE Type C; master; 00:30:00; inside_albany_0504 (Box 47)
    - No. 820, 1981-11-06; 1 inch videotape: SMPTE Type C; master; 00:30:00; inside_albany_0504 (Box 47)
    - No. 821, 1981-11-13; 1 inch videotape: SMPTE Type C; master; 00:30:00; inside_albany_0504 (Box 47)
    - No. 822, 1981-11-21; 1 inch videotape: SMPTE Type C; master; 00:30:00; inside_albany_0505 (Box 47)
    - No. 823, 1981-11-28; 1 inch videotape: SMPTE Type C; master; 00:30:00; inside_albany_0505 (Box 47)
    - No. 824, 1981-12-05; 1 inch videotape: SMPTE Type C; master; 00:30:00; inside_albany_0505 (Box 47)
    - No. 825, 1981-12-12; 1 inch videotape: SMPTE Type C; master; 00:30:00; inside_albany_0506 (Box 48)
    - No. 826, 1981-12-18; 1 inch videotape: SMPTE Type C; master; 00:30:00; inside_albany_0506 (Box 48)
    - No. 827, 1981-12-24; 1 inch videotape: SMPTE Type C; master; 00:30:00; inside_albany_0506 (Box 48)
    - No. 828, 1981-12-31; 1 inch videotape: SMPTE Type C; master; 00:30:00; inside_albany_0507 (Box 48)
  - Videorecordings, 1982
    - No. 829, 1982-01-08; 1 inch videotape: SMPTE Type C; master; 00:30:00; inside_albany_0507 (Box 48)
    - No. 829, 1982-01-08; 1 inch videotape: SMPTE Type C; dub; 00:30:00; inside_albany_0507; duplicate (Box 48)
    - No. 830, 1982-01-16; 3/4 inch videotape: U-matic; master; 00:30:00; inside_albany_0339 (Box 36)
    - No. 831, 1982-01-22; 1 inch videotape: SMPTE Type C; master; 00:30:00; inside_albany_0508 (Box 48)
    - No. 832, 1982-01-29; 1 inch videotape: SMPTE Type C; master; 00:30:00; inside_albany_0508 (Box 48)
    - No. 833, 1982-02-05; 1 inch videotape: SMPTE Type C; master; 00:30:00; inside_albany_0508 (Box 48)
    - No. 834, 1982-02-12; 1 inch videotape: SMPTE Type C; master; 00:30:00; inside_albany_0509 (Box 48)
    - No. 835, 1982-02-19; 1 inch videotape: SMPTE Type C; master; 00:30:00; inside_albany_0509 (Box 48)
    - No. 836, 1982-02-26; 1 inch videotape: SMPTE Type C; master; 00:30:00; inside_albany_0509 (Box 48)
    - No. 837, 1982-03-05; 1 inch videotape: SMPTE Type C; master; 00:30:00; inside_albany_0510 (Box 48)
    - No. 838, 1982-03-12; 1 inch videotape: SMPTE Type C; master; 00:30:00; inside_albany_0510 (Box 48)
    - No. 839, 1982-03-19; 1 inch videotape: SMPTE Type C; master; 00:30:00; inside_albany_0510 (Box 48)
    - No. 840, 1982-03-26; 1 inch videotape: SMPTE Type C; master; 00:30:00; inside_albany_0511 (Box 48)
    - No. 841, 1982-04-02; 1 inch videotape: SMPTE Type C; master; 00:30:00; inside_albany_0511 (Box 48)
    - No. 842, 1982-04-09; 1 inch videotape: SMPTE Type C; master; 00:30:00; inside_albany_0511 (Box 48)
    - No. 843, 1982-04-16; 1 inch videotape: SMPTE Type C; master; 00:30:00; inside_albany_0512 (Box 48)
    - No. 844, 1982-04-23; 1 inch videotape: SMPTE Type C; master; 00:30:00; inside_albany_0512 (Box 48)
    - No. 845, 1982-04-30; 1 inch videotape: SMPTE Type C; master; 00:30:00; inside_albany_0512 (Box 48)
    - No. 846, 1982-05-07; 1 inch videotape: SMPTE Type C; master; 00:30:00; inside_albany_0513 (Box 48)
    - No. 847, 1982-05-14; 1 inch videotape: SMPTE Type C; master; 00:30:00; inside_albany_0513 (Box 48)
    - No. 848, 1982-05-21; 1 inch videotape: SMPTE Type C; master; 00:30:00; inside_albany_0513 (Box 48)
    - No. 849, 1982-05-29; 1 inch videotape: SMPTE Type C; master; 00:30:00; inside_albany_0514 (Box 49)
    - No. 850, 1982-06-05; 1 inch videotape: SMPTE Type C; master; 00:30:00; inside_albany_0514 (Box 49)
    - No. 851, 1982-06-12; 1 inch videotape: SMPTE Type C; master; 00:30:00; inside_albany_0514 (Box 49)
    - No. 852, 1982-06-18; 3/4 inch videotape: U-matic; master; 00:30:00; inside_albany_0340 (Box 36)
    - No. 901, 1982-06-25; 1 inch videotape: SMPTE Type C; master; 00:30:00; inside_albany_0515 (Box 49)
    - No. 902, 1982-07-02; 1 inch videotape: SMPTE Type C; master; 00:30:00; inside_albany_0515 (Box 49)
    - No. 903, 1982-07-09; 1 inch videotape: SMPTE Type C; master; 00:30:00; inside_albany_0515 (Box 49)
    - No. 904, 1982-07-16; 1 inch videotape: SMPTE Type C; master; 00:30:00; inside_albany_0516 (Box 49)
    - No. 905, 1982-07-23; 1 inch videotape: SMPTE Type C; master; 00:30:00; inside_albany_0516 (Box 49)
    - No. 906, 1982-07-30; 1 inch videotape: SMPTE Type C; master; 00:30:00; inside_albany_0516 (Box 49)
    - No. 907, 1982-08-06; 1 inch videotape: SMPTE Type C; master; 00:30:00; inside_albany_0517 (Box 49)